Hello friends, ICICI Lombard General
Insurance has disclosed its quarter two numbers
and has
also announced a dividend of ₹ 50 paise,
which is once again
good news for the investors. If we
talk about the figures, all these figures are
in lakhs, so we will convert them into crores and
talk about these numbers. If we talk about the
total income, then here their income is
seen to be something like 5850 crores
and if we talk about the same
period last year, then their income was seen to be something like 5050 crores
and if we
talk about the last quarter, then
their income is seen to be something like 5300 51 crores. So, if we
look at it year after year, then the income is
increasing well, around 20 percent
income was seen increasing,
whereas if we talk about their expenses, then
their expenses were seen to be something like 5186 crores,
while talking about the same period last year.  If we talk about
its expenses, then 4453 crores were seen, if we
talk about the last quarter, then
its expenses were seen to be around 4850 crores,
if we talk about
its net profit, then its net
profit can be said to be 693 crores,
something of 694 crores was seen in this quarter,
whereas if we talk about the same period last year, then
its net
profit was seen to be something of 577 crores and if we talk about the
same last quarter, then
its PAT was seen to be 580 crores, if we talk about year after year, then
here PAT has also been
seen with a growth of around 20%, meaning
again, although the stock has been seen trading today at % down,
but if we talk about it, then the
result is good in a sense and is
around or above the market expectation,
so somewhere on Monday there can be a good
action in the stock, whereas if we talk about
its earnings per share, then its earnings
per share on diluted basis is
seen to be 1388  They are available and if we talk about the same
period last year then it was ₹1 70 paise and if we
talk about their last quarter then it was ₹
68 so a decent change of around ₹ has been seen in EPS also on the
top side
so these were
their ah quarter two numbers to
get the IIC Lombard numbers first and accurate
please subscribe to the channel
thank you